

Software Engineer

email: yuva.chang@gmail.comphone: 352 514 1413address: Brooklyn, NY, 11216website: https://yuvachang.comgithub: https://github.com/yuvachanglinkedin: www.linkedin.com/in/yuvachang

Skills

Javascript, React, Redux, Express, Node.js, HTML5, CSS3, SASS, Git, Firebase, Cloud Firestore, Sequelize, PSQL, SQL, MongoDb, Mongoose, Heroku, Webpack, Web Development, React.js, Redux.js, Node, HTML, CSS, PostgreSQL, Sequel, GitHub, Rhino, VRay, Photoshop, Illustrator, Indesign, AutoCAD

Projects

Minesweeper - Deployed: https://minesweeper.yuvachang.com Github: https://github.com/yuvachang/minesweeper

React, Redux, Firebase/Firestore, Node.js, SASS.

Replicates original Minesweeper game with fidelity in mind. I ensured smooth gameplay with event listeners for board evaluations. Original mouse functionality includes: R+LMB clicks open surrounding cells if flag counts match mine counts and scoreboard to track top-times, RMB sets flags, R+LMB highlights surrounding cells, LMB-up opens cell.

- Recursive cascade of open cells if cell with no neighboring mines is opened. First click of game always incurs cascade to improve game-start experience--never click a mine on first click.
- · Firestore leaderboard to track top scores and live updates.

Split - Deployed: https://split.yuvachang.com Github: https://github.com/yuvachang/split

React, Redux, Firebase/Firestore, Node.js, SASS.

Consolidates and manages group/individual receipts. Live-editing of receipts and real-time calculation of user debts as amounts are updated. Personal project to learn Firebase and achieve MVP with mobile responsiveness.

• Features include: email & Google login, friend management with live notifications, local and DB data queries, data creation/deletion, live editing using Firestore listeners.

EZ-Split - Deployed: https://ezsplit.herokuapp.com Github: https://github.com/EZSplit/EZSplit

React, Redux, Express, Socket.IO, Sequelize, PSQL, Mongoose, MongoDB, Passport, Node.js.

3-week team project achieving MVP using AGILE methods. Itemize and manage receipts using an OCR api and live-editing using websockets. Contributions:

- · Implemented real-time editing using Socket.io and wrote front end components for multi-user editing.
- Wrote code for calculating debts and user IOUs as they updated from the socket connections.
- · Implemented the OCR API on back end and routes for parsing/handling JSON receipt data.
- · Created MongoDB schemas and queries for handling image, users, and groups data.

Github Browser (Android) - Github: https://github.com/yuvachang/RN_GitHub_Browser video demo: https://bit.ly/2XCKdhs React Native, Redux, Node.js, and Android Studio.

React Native Android app for logging into GitHub using basic authentication and viewing user repositories and subdirectories. 4 day stackathon: I learned React Native and its navigation for a smooth auth- and user-flow.v

Work Experience

Architectural Rendering - Freelance, New York, NY: 01/2018-12/2018

- Rendered interior or exterior perspectives for client or competition based work.
- · Visualisations of materials and iterations for clients to show design and space options.
- Modeled plans, sections, schematics to 3D with Rhino and VRay, and post-processed in Photoshop.

SGVA - Junior Architect, New York, NY: 11/2015-10/2017

- Streamlined the 2D to 3D workflow and shaped the rendering language within the firm by introducing Rhino+Vray.
- · Increased efficiency of meeting marketing and client proposal deadlines with digital deliverables.
- · Coordinated and met regularly with contractors and manufacturers to maintain schedule on residential work.
- Worked on CAD documents, specs, code, and digital work for residential projects and multi-family developments.
- Developed and put together drawing sets for competition submissions.

Redtop Architects - Design Intern, New York, NY: 04-08/2014

- · Built physical and digital models, and produced renderings for marketing and client work.
- · Contributed to construction drawing sets.

Education

Fullstack Academy of Code 01/2019-04/2019

Full stack web development immersive covering Javascript technologies, databases, and Agile methods.

University of Michigan, Taubman College of Architecture 2013-2015

Master of Architecture

University of Florida 2008-2012

Bachelor of Design in Architecture

Minor in Japanese East Asian Languages and Literatures